<resources>
    <string name="app_name">KK</string>
    <!-- 4. Add a string resource for kics, for the buttons-->
    <string name="click_me_text"> Click on me! </string>
    <string name="submit_button_text">Submit</string>
    <string name="biodata_text">I utilize my experience and knowledge to make a strong, positive impact
        to the strategic and tactical objectives of the organization that I work in. I have a wealth of technical skills,
        problem solving skills, and development experience in C, C++, Java, C#, .NET, databases and UNIX systems programming.
        In addition to this, I have experience in areas of customer support and sustenance engineering.
        I am extremely result oriented and have strong communication, technical writing, and negotiation skills.
    MS-DOS and Windows use a common text file format, with each line of text separated by a two-character combination: carriage return (CR) and line feed (LF). It is common for the last line of text not to be terminated with a CR-LF marker, and many text editors (including Notepad) do not automatically insert one on the last line.
On Microsoft Windows operating systems, a file is regarded as a text file if the suffix of the name of the file (the "filename extension") is "txt". However, many other suffixes are used for text files with specific purposes. For example, source code for computer programs is usually kept in text files that have file name suffixes indicating the programming language in which the source is written.
Most Windows text files use "ANSI", "OEM", "Unicode" or "UTF-8" encoding. What Windows terminology calls "ANSI encodings" are usually single-byte ISO-8859 encodings (i.e. ANSI in the Microsoft Notepad menus is really "System Code Page", non-Unicode, legacy encoding), except for in locales such as Chinese, Japanese and Korean that require double-byte character sets. ANSI encodings were traditionally used as default system locales within Windows, before the transition to Unicode. By contrast, OEM encodings, also known as MS-DOS code pages, were defined by IBM for use in the original IBM PC text mode display system. They typically include graphical and line-drawing characters common in (possibly full-screen) MS-DOS applications. "Unicode"-encoded Windows text files contain text in UTF-16 Unicode Transformation Format. Such files normally begin with Byte Order Mark (BOM), which communicates the endianness of the file content. Although UTF-8 does not suffer from endianness problems, many Windows programs (i.e. Notepad) prepend the contents of UTF-8-encoded files with BOM,[2] to differentiate UTF-8 encoding from other 8-bit encodings.[3]

    </string>
</resources>
